adventuresbydisney.com 2006-12-30

# Privacy Policy for Disney Theme Parks and Resorts

|  |  |  |  |   
---  
Privacy Policy/Your California Privacy Rights  
Welcome! Below you will find separate privacy policies for the Walt Disney Internet Group (WDIG) and Disney Theme Parks and Resorts. The privacy policy for WDIG applies to all information collected on this site. The privacy policy for Disney Theme Parks and Resorts applies to certain information collected directly by Disney Theme Parks and Resorts, including through offline transactions.

As a reminder, the WDIG privacy policy was updated on November 6, 2003. If you registered prior to that date and have not accepted the updated WDIG privacy policy, please refer to the previous WDIG privacy policy.  
  
|  |  |  |  | WDIG Privacy Policy |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
---  
**Effective Date: 11/06/03**

For over 75 years, The Walt Disney Company has taken great pride in the relationships that it has developed with its guests. In keeping with this tradition, we at the Walt Disney Internet Group are dedicated to protecting your privacy and handling any personal information we obtain from you with care and respect. This Privacy Policy is designed to answer your questions regarding our privacy policies and principles. 

We recognize the need to provide additional protections for children who visit our sites. To read about our privacy protections for kids under the age of 13, [click here](http://disney.go.com/corporate/privacy/kids.html?ppLink=pp_wdpro) to read the Walt Disney Internet Group Kids Privacy Policy.   
  
| Q1. | What information does this Privacy Policy cover?  
---|---  
A1. | Except as specifically described below in A2 and A6, this Privacy Policy applies only to personally identifiable information collected on the Web sites where this Privacy Policy is posted and does not apply to any other information collected by The Walt Disney Family of Companies through any other means. This Privacy Policy applies to use and sharing of personally identifiable information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted. However, for guests who registered on our Web sites prior to the date that this Privacy Policy is posted, we will apply this Privacy Policy to personally identifiable information associated with that account only if the guest accepts the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Once the guest has accepted these terms and conditions, this Privacy Policy will also apply to personally identifiable information collected from that guest prior to the date that this Privacy Policy is posted. In a similar fashion, we will apply this Privacy Policy to personally identifiable information collected in the course of Non-Registered Transactions (as defined in A3 below) that occurred prior to the date that this Privacy Policy is posted, but only if the guest accepts the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

As used in this Privacy Policy, "The Walt Disney Family of Companies" includes The Walt Disney Company and all of its subsidiary and affiliated entities, including companies such as ABC and ESPN that generally do not offer their products and services under the "Disney" brand name, as well as companies that generally do offer their products and services under the "Disney" brand name. (At times, our Web sites refer to The Walt Disney Family of Companies as "The Walt Disney family of companies.") The Walt Disney Internet Group (including its subsidiaries) is a member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies, and is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we," "us," "our," and "ourselves."

In keeping with the traditions of The Walt Disney Company, we refer to customers of The Walt Disney Family of Companies as "guests." When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as the individual's name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number. When other information, such as, for example, consumer product preferences, or number of children, is directly associated with personally identifiable information, this other information also becomes personally identifiable information for purposes of this Privacy Policy. Personally identifiable information is sometimes referred to in this Privacy Policy as "personal information." Finally, the terms of this Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable laws.   
  
back to top of policy  
Q2. | What types of personally identifiable information do we collect about our guests?  
A2. | We collect several types of personally identifiable information about our guests. _Information You Provide to Us_

Much of the personally identifiable information we receive comes directly from guests who are interested in obtaining various products and services from us. Typically, this information includes the guest's name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number. We may also collect other types of information such as gender, age, number of children, and personal interests, which we may associate with personally identifiable information. If you purchase products or services from us, we'll note, for example, credit card information, the type of services or products ordered or purchased, and the date of the order or purchase. We collect personal information when you register on, log on, or visit our Web sites, including when you participate in activities on our Web sites, such as sweepstakes, contests, games and promotional offers.

 _Information Collected Through Technology_

We collect information through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to one of our sites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information.

Our Web sites also use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the Web site. We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, when you return to one of our sites after logging in, cookies provide information to the site so that the site will remember who you are. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your Web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services will not function properly.

Our Web sites use a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Web sites. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on our Web sites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our Web sites. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send our guests to determine whether our guests have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

Many advertisements are managed and placed on our Web sites by third parties. These companies are called "network advertisers." Network advertisers who place advertisements on our Web sites may also use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information when you click on or move your cursor over one of their banner advertisements. You may not realize this information is being collected. In some cases, we may have access to information from Web beacons and cookies used by network advertisers on our sites and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited that are also associated with the network advertiser. Finally, once you've clicked on an advertisement and have left our Web sites, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site.

 _Information That We Collect from Others_

We may supplement personally identifiable information that we have collected directly from our guests with other information that we obtain from third parties and other members of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. In addition, we may obtain information about individuals who are not yet users of our Web sites or guests of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. In addition, when we associate information that we obtain from third parties or other members of The Walt Disney Family of Companies with personally identifiable information that we have collected under this Privacy Policy, we will treat the acquired information like the information that we collected ourselves and, except as permitted by this Privacy Policy, the information will not be shared with third parties.   
  
back to top of policy  
Q3. | How is your personally identifiable information used and shared?  
A3. | As described in detail below, The Walt Disney Family of Companies may use your personally identifiable information in many ways, including sending you promotional materials, and sharing your information with third parties so that these third parties can send you promotional materials. (By "promotional materials," we mean communications that directly promote the use of our Web sites, or the purchase of products or services.) As outlined below in A4, you may "opt-out" of certain uses of your personal information. _Disney Family of Companies, Licensees and Co-Branding Participants_

Personally identifiable information collected under this Privacy Policy is shared among and used by The Walt Disney Family of Companies for many purposes. For example, The Walt Disney Family of Companies may use your personal information to send you promotional materials about goods and services (including special offers and promotions) either offered by The Walt Disney Family of Companies or offered by third parties. These promotional materials may be sent to you by postal mail, e-mail or other means. You may opt out of receiving these communications as provided in A4 below. Please keep in mind, however, that when you purchase or request products or services from The Walt Disney Family of Companies, promotional materials may accompany delivery of that product or service. We refer to sending you promotional materials in these circumstances as "Fulfillment Uses" of your personal information. Because these promotional materials accompany products or services that you have requested, your opt-outs for Individual Disney Companies and The Walt Disney Family of Companies under A4 below will not apply to any of these Fulfillment Uses.

The Walt Disney Family of Companies may also use your personal information for many purposes other than sending you promotional materials. (We refer to all of these types of uses of your personal information that do not involve the sending of promotional materials as "Operational Uses.") For example, we may use your information to complete transactions requested by you (such as your purchase of a product or service offered on our Web sites), or to send you administrative communications either about your account with us or about features of our Web sites, including any future changes to this Privacy Policy. As another example of Operational Uses, we may share your personal information with the Walt Disney World © Resort telephone reservations center so that the reservations center operators are able to respond immediately to your questions or requests when you call, rather than asking you to provide your information a second time. Because these uses of your personal information do not involve sending you promotional materials, your opt-outs for Individual Disney Companies and The Walt Disney Family of Companies under A4 below will not apply to any of these Operational Uses.

In addition to using your personal information within The Walt Disney Family of Companies, The Walt Disney Family of Companies may share your personal information with companies that offer products and/or services under brand names of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. These companies are called "licensees." For example, a company that publishes and sells books under the "Disney" brand would be such a licensee. The Walt Disney Family of Companies may also share your information with companies that offer products and/or services that are co-branded using brand names of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. These companies are called "co-branding participants." For example, the Disney's Visa Card is co-branded with the bank that issues that credit card. When The Walt Disney Family of Companies shares personal information with third parties acting as licensees and co-branding participants, these licensees and co-branding participants are restricted by contract from using the personal information for any marketing or promotional purpose that is not related to a licensed or co-branded product or service. Finally, to further protect your privacy, these licensees and co-branding participants' use of personal information shared with them under this Privacy Policy is subject to the same opt-out rights (and limitations upon those rights) that apply to use of personal information by members of The Walt Disney Family of Companies under A4 below.

You may engage in transactions (such as purchasing products or services) without registering and logging on our Web sites. These transactions may be either with us or with other members of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. (We refer to all of these transactions that you engage in without registering and logging on our Web sites as "Non-Registered Transactions.") An example of a Non-Registered Transaction would be when you purchase items from DisneyShopping.com without registering and logging on that Web site. When you engage in Non-Registered Transactions, the opt-out choices described in A4 below will not be available to you, but your information will not be shared with third parties, and will not be used by any member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies to send you promotional materials other than the member involved in your transaction, except as separately permitted by other provisions of this Privacy Policy.

Finally, The Walt Disney Family of Companies may take your personally identifiable information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you (de-personalizing your information). Given the nature of this information, there are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy upon the right of The Walt Disney Family of Companies to aggregate or de-personalize your personal information, and The Walt Disney Family of Companies may use and/or share with third parties the resulting non-personally identifiable information in any way.

 _Third Parties Offering Promotions, Products, or Services_

Subject to your opt-out choices (see A4 below), The Walt Disney Family of Companies may share your personal information with selected third parties so that they can send you promotional materials about goods and services (including special offers and promotions) offered by them. (We call this type of sharing "promotional sharing" or sharing for "promotional purposes.") When sharing your information for promotional purposes, The Walt Disney Family of Companies attempts to select only reputable companies that offer high quality products and services. Moreover, The Walt Disney Family of Companies will not share your e-mail address with third parties for promotional purposes, except when you consent to such sharing in the course of your participation in a Sponsored Activity as described below. When The Walt Disney Family of Companies shares your personal information with a third party under any circumstance described in this "Third Parties Offering Promotions, Products, or Services" section, your personal information will become permanently subject to the information use and sharing practices of the third party, and the third party will not be restricted by this Privacy Policy with respect to its use and further sharing of your personal information.

In addition to the promotional sharing that is subject to your opt-out choices under A4 below, The Walt Disney Family of Companies may also share your information when you engage in certain activities on our sites that are sponsored by third parties, such as purchasing products or services offered by a third party, electing to receive information or communications from a third party, or electing to participate in contests, sweepstakes, games or other programs sponsored in whole or in part by a third party. The Walt Disney Family of Companies may also share your personal information when you respond to promotional materials from The Walt Disney Family of Companies and authorize a third party to use your personal information for purposes such as, for example, sending you additional promotional materials, providing you a product or service, or entering you in a contest, sweepstakes or game. (We refer to all of these activities and requests as "Sponsored Activities.") When you participate in Sponsored Activities, you will either be required or requested to agree that the sponsor or business associate may use your personal information (including, in some cases, your e-mail address) in accordance with the sponsor or business associate's privacy practices. Since you will have consented to this specific instance of sharing of your personal information, the opt-out choice for "Third Parties" described in A4 below will not apply.

 _Companies That Facilitate Communications and Transactions with You_

Sometimes The Walt Disney Family of Companies hires companies to help deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package or a company that helps fulfill prizes for a sweepstakes. In those instances, there is a need to share your information with these companies. Sometimes The Walt Disney Family of Companies also works with other companies who help either gather your information or communicate with you. Your opt-out choices under A4 below will not apply to sharing by The Walt Disney Family of Companies of your personal information with any of these companies. Nonetheless, except as separately permitted by other provisions of this Privacy Policy, these companies are allowed to gather, receive, and use your information only for the purposes described in this paragraph or as required by law.

 _Companies That You Previously Authorized to Obtain Your Information_

In certain circumstances, your dealings with a third party may have authorized that third party to obtain your personal information from The Walt Disney Family of Companies and to use that information in accordance with the third party's own privacy practices and policies. For example, in using an online shopping service (such as the shopping services offered by Internet portals that refer the portal's users to third-party merchants), you may have authorized that shopping service to obtain from the service's participating third-party merchants (including The Walt Disney Family of Companies) information about your purchases conducted through the shopping service. In such circumstances, your opt-out elections under A4 below will not apply to sharing of your personal information by The Walt Disney Family of Companies. Nonetheless, The Walt Disney Family of Companies will provide such companies only the information that you authorized (except as separately permitted under other provisions of this Privacy Policy). In the example given above, the shopping service would be provided only information concerning purchases you made from The Walt Disney Family of Companies through that shopping service, and would not be provided any other information concerning you, unless any additional sharing of your personal information were separately permitted under another provision of this Privacy Policy.

 _Purchase or Sale of Businesses_

From time to time, we may purchase a business or sell one or more of our businesses and your personally identifiable information may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale. In the event that we purchase a business, the personally identifiable information received with that business would be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy, if it is practicable and permissible to do so. In the event that we sell a business, we will include provisions in the selling contract requiring the purchaser to treat your personally identifiable information in the same manner required by this Privacy Policy (including any amendments to this Privacy Policy). In light of this protection, your opt-out choices under A4 will not affect our right to transfer your information to a purchaser in these circumstances. The provisions of this paragraph will also apply in the event that one or more businesses of any other member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies are sold and personal information subject to this Privacy Policy is transferred to a purchaser of those businesses.

 _Disclosures Required By Law and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Web Sites, The Walt Disney Family of Companies and Others_

Regardless of any opt-out choices that you make under A4, The Walt Disney Family of Companies will disclose personal information when it believes in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce our Terms of Use; enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules; protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or, protect the safety and security of our Web sites, The Walt Disney Family of Companies, and/or third parties, including the safety and security of property that belongs to The Walt Disney Family of Companies or third parties.   
  
back to top of policy  
Q4. | What choices do you have about the collection, use, and sharing of your personally identifiable information?  
A4. | With regard to personal information that you have provided under this Privacy Policy, there are three separate opt-out choices available to you. These opt-out choices are the means by which you give us, or decline to give us, your consent to use your personal information for the purposes covered by these opt-out choices. Some of our Web sites may not present you all three opt-out choices described below. Please be assured, however, that if any one of these opt-out choices is not presented to you on a Web site, personal information collected from you on that site will not be used for the purposes covered by that opt-out choice. There are several methods by which you can exercise your opt-out choices: (a) during the registration process on our Web sites; (b) after registration, by logging on our Web sites, clicking on our Privacy Policy links, going to a site's Guest Services center (sometimes called a site's "Member Services" or "Preference" center), and following the opt-out directions; and (c) as described below in A6. Each of these opt-out choices is subject to the exceptions described further below in this A4.

Your three opt-out choices are:

 _Third Parties_ : You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from third parties. If you do not choose this opt-out, The Walt Disney Family of Companies may share your personal information so that third parties can send you these promotional materials. Your opt-out choices for third parties are specific to the particular Web sites where you make these choices. Thus, if you want to opt out of all uses of your personal information covered by the "Third Parties" opt-out, you must consistently elect that opt-out at each of our Web sites where you either register, or log in and visit the Guest Services center. If you want to make a change in your "Third Parties" opt-out choices, you will need to make that change at each of our Web sites where you previously made a different choice. Please bear in mind that this opt-out choice for "Third Parties" will not apply to the licensees and co-branding participants described above in A3. _The Walt Disney Family of Companies_ : You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from members of The Walt Disney Family of Companies, including the licensees and co-branding participants described above in A3. This opt-out choice is found on each of our Web sites. For your convenience, when you make a choice regarding this The Walt Disney Family of Companies" opt-out at any one of our Web sites, we will treat that choice as replacing any other choices regarding that opt-out that that you may previously have made. Thus, if you want to make a change in your "The Walt Disney Family of Companies" opt-out choice, you can make that change by visiting the Guest Services center at any one of our Web sites. Your election to choose this "The Walt Disney Family of Companies" opt-out will not, however, override your consent to receive promotional materials from a specific member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. As described in the following paragraph, you provide this consent when you visit the Guest Services center of the Web site for a specific member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies and choose not to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from that specific member. _Individual Disney Companies_ : You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional materials directly from a specific member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies. To do so, you must visit the Guest Services center of the Web site for this specific member and opt-out of receiving promotional materials from this member. However, if you do not also opt-out of receiving promotional materials from "The Walt Disney Family of Companies" as described in the preceding paragraph, you may still receive promotional materials from this specific member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies.

Please keep in mind that any opt-out choices you make will not apply in situations where (a) you either have made, simultaneously make, or later make a specific request for information from a member of The Walt Disney Family of Companies, (b) The Walt Disney Family of Companies uses your personal information for either "Operational Uses" or "Fulfillment Uses" (as described above in A3), (c) you either have engaged, simultaneously engage, or later engage in either Non-Registered Transactions or Sponsored Activities (as described above in A3), or (d) The Walt Disney Family of Companies shares your personal information under the provisions of A3 above with respect to "Companies That Facilitate Communications and Transactions With You," "Companies That You Previously Authorized to Obtain Your Information," "Third Party Advertisers and Network Advertisers," "Purchase or Sale of Businesses," or "Disclosures Required By Law and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Web Sites, The Walt Disney Family of Companies and Others."

Finally, if you do not exercise your opt-out choices upon registration or initial log-in at our Web sites, it may take up to ninety (90) days for your opt-out choices to be fully effective. Our systems require time to update, and promotional mailings using personal information shared before your opt-out may already be in process. Thus, you might continue to receive promotional materials from The Walt Disney Family of Companies based upon the personal information you have provided under this Privacy Policy for up to ninety (90) days. For similar reasons, your personal information might continue to be shared with third parties for promotional purposes for up to ninety (90) days.   
  
back to top of policy  
Q5. | What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your personally identifiable information?  
A5. | The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect guest information from unauthorized access and improper use. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.   
back to top of policy  
Q6. | How can you update your contact information and opt out choices?  
A6. | You can access and update the contact information you gave us during registration (that is, your postal address, e-mail address, or any other information that would directly enable us to contact you), or modify your opt-out choices, by going to our member services centers. Simply click on this link <https://register.go.com/go/memberservices/home>, or go to the Guest Services centers on our Web sites, and then log in with your member name and password. There are instructions on the start page of the link above to help you recover your password if you've forgotten it. If you need to recover your password, you can also contact us via e-mail at [ms_support@help.go.com](mailto:ms_support@help.go.com). Please include information in the e-mail that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your request. We may also provide you an opportunity to update your contact information and/or modify your opt-out choices by sending you an e-mail or other communication that invites your response. Finally, you may unsubscribe from certain e-mail communications by clicking on unsubscribe links in those e-mails.   
back to top of policy  
Q7. | How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy?  
A7. | If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to [ms_support@help.go.com](mailto:ms_support@help.go.com) or write us:  

Member Services  
WDIG  
500 S. Buena Vista St.  
Mail Code 7716  
Burbank, CA 91521-7716  

Please be assured that any personal information that you provide in communications to the above e-mail and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you so request.   
back to top of policy  
Q8. | How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?  
A8. | We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Web sites covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on the Web sites covered by this Privacy Policy. Please note that, at all times, you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us your current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us.

The Walt Disney Internet Group is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html.   
  
back to top of policy  
  
* * *

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of the Walt Disney Internet Group (including Movies.com, LLC) who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [caprivacy.wdig@twdc.com](mailto:caprivacy.wdig@twdc.com) or write us: 

WDIG CA Privacy Rights  
500 S. Buena Vista St.  
Mail Code 7716  
Burbank, CA 91521-7716 
  
back to top of page    
|   
---  
Privacy Policy for  Walt Disney Parks and Resorts Online;  Walt Disney Parks and Resorts, LLC;  Walt Disney Travel Co., Inc.;  Walt Disney World Co.;  Magical Cruise Company, Limited   
|  |  |   
---  
**Effective Date: 1/1/2005**  
This Privacy Policy is designed to answer your questions regarding our privacy practices and principles. Walt Disney Parks and Resorts, LLC, Walt Disney Parks and Resorts Online, Walt Disney Travel Co., Inc., Walt Disney World Co. and Magical Cruise Company, Limited are referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we," "us," "our" and "ourselves." In keeping with the traditions of The Walt Disney Company, we refer to our customers as "guests." When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as the individual's name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number. When other information, such as, for example, consumer product preferences, or number of children, is directly associated with personally identifiable information, this other information also becomes personally identifiable information for purposes of this Privacy Policy. Personally identifiable information is sometimes referred to in this Privacy Policy as "personal information." Finally, the terms of this Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable laws.  
|  Scope of Privacy Policy   
---  
Q1. | What information does this Privacy Policy cover?  
A1. | This Privacy Policy applies to all personally identifiable information that we collect, on or after the effective date of this Privacy Policy, from individuals who provide us such information for the purpose of obtaining from us a product or service primarily for personal, family or household purposes. This Privacy Policy also applies to all personally identifiable information that we obtain from the Walt Disney Internet Group ("WDIG") on or after the effective date of this Privacy Policy.   
back to top of policy  
Information We Collect   
Q2. | What types of personal information may we collect?  
A2. | We may collect various types of personal information. For example, we may receive personal information that comes directly from guests who are interested in obtaining various products and services from us. This information may include, without limitation, the guest's name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number. We also may collect other types of information such as gender, age, number of children, and personal interests, which we may associate with personal information. If you purchase products or services from us, we may note, for example, credit card information, the type of services or products ordered or purchased, and the date of the order or purchase. In addition, we may collect personal information from you if you participate in sweepstakes, contests, games or promotional offers.   
back to top of policy  

Q3. | How may we use and share your personal information that we collect?  
A3. | We may use and share your personal information collected under this Privacy Policy in a variety of ways, including, without limitation, for example: 

  * We may send you promotional materials, and we may share your personal information with other subsidiaries of The Walt Disney Company and third parties so that they can send you promotional materials. (By "promotional materials," we mean communications that directly promote the purchase of products or services.) These promotional materials may concern our products and services, and/or the products and services of another subsidiary of The Walt Disney Company or a third party. These promotional materials may be sent to you by postal mail, e-mail or other means. 
  * We may use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than sending you promotional materials. For example: 
    * We may use your information to complete transactions requested by you, or to send you administrative communications about any account you may have with us or about future changes to this Privacy Policy. 
    * We may hire companies to help deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package or a company that helps fulfill prizes for a sweepstakes. In those instances, there is a need to share your information with these companies. Sometimes we also may work with other companies who help either gather your information or communicate with you. 
    * We may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including, without limitation, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions and/or game rules; protect your safety or security, including, without limitation, the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or protect the safety and security of us, other subsidiaries of The Walt Disney Company, and/or third parties, including, without limitation, the safety and security of property that belongs to us, other subsidiaries of The Walt Disney Company or third parties. 
  * We may take your personal information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you (de-personalizing your information). We may use this non-personally identifiable information for, among other purposes, research and analysis to improve our products and services. 

From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to "opt in" to, or to "opt out" from, certain uses by us of your personal information and/or our sharing of your personal information with other subsidiaries of The Walt Disney Company and/or third parties.   
back to top of policy  
Information We Obtain from WDIG   
Q4. | What types of personal information may we obtain from WDIG?  
A4. | We may obtain from WDIG the same types of personal information that we collect directly from our guests, as described in A2 of this Privacy Policy.   
back to top of policy  

Q5. | How may we use and share personal information that we obtain from WDIG?  
A5. | You may have provided personal information online to WDIG. Our use and sharing of personal information regarding you that we obtain from WDIG is subject to WDIG's privacy policy (the "WDIG Privacy Policy") and any choices you made under the WDIG Privacy Policy (including, without limitation, the choices described in A4 of the WDIG Privacy Policy). To read the WDIG Privacy Policy, click here.   
back to top of policy  
Amendments to Privacy Policy   
Q6. | How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?  
A6. | We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we amend this Privacy Policy to permit material changes in the way we collect, use and/or share your personal information, we will notify you of such changes by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided to us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Web site. Any such material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective thirty (30) calendar days following either our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or our posting of notice of the changes on our Web site. Any such material changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use and sharing of personal information that you provided to us before our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit material changes in our collection, use or sharing of personal information that you have provided to us before the effective date of such changes, you must so notify us before that effective date. Please be advised, however, that, regardless of whether you provide such notice to us, the changes to this Privacy Policy will apply to any personal information that you provide to us on or after the effective date of such changes.   
back to top of policy  
California Privacy Rights   
Q7. | Do California residents have special rights?  
A7. | Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [caprivacy.wdw@twdc.com](mailto:caprivacy.wdw@twdc.com) or write us: 

Walt Disney Parks and Resorts  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
P.O. Box 10455  
Lake Buena Vista, FL 32830 
  
back to top of policy  
back to top of page
